<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to the SPC home page! on Sports Programming Club</title>
    <link>https://spcubco.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to the SPC home page! on Sports Programming Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 10:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://spcubco.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetings 2020</title>
      <link>https://spcubco.github.io/posts/2019/09/meetings-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spcubco.github.io/posts/2019/09/meetings-2020/</guid>
      <description> This page will be updated with the content of the meetings.
The password asked to join the contest is &amp;ldquo;okanagan&amp;rdquo;, without quotes.
Meeting 8  Dijkstra&amp;rsquo;s algorithm Dijkstra&amp;rsquo;s algorithm for sparse graphs Try your Dijkstra implementation here Maze problem Example of Dijkstra with a twist  Meeting 6  Discussion of Prefix Sum Discussion of Fenwick Tree Try cumulative sums here Try your Fenwick Tree here Inversion Count  Meeting 5  Implementation of Kruskal&amp;rsquo;s algorithm Discussion of Kruskal&amp;rsquo;s Test your implementation here  Meeting 4  Contest Geeks for Geeks Implementation Problem 1 Problem 2 Problem 3 Problem 4  Meeting 3  Contest  Meeting 2  Contest  Meeting 1  Contest  Useful Links  uHunt Competitive Programming Book VisuAlgo Training Sheet  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetings 2019</title>
      <link>https://spcubco.github.io/posts/2019/01/meetings-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spcubco.github.io/posts/2019/01/meetings-2019/</guid>
      <description>This page will be updated with the content of the meetings.
The password asked to join the contest is &amp;ldquo;okanagan&amp;rdquo;, without quotes.
Meeting 9 In this meeting, we will not use vjudge. Instead, we will use problems from Univerity of Erechim&amp;rsquo;s online judge (URI). We opted to do that because after searching on the internet, there were not many problems that were straightforward DFS/BFS problems. Hence, we opted to pick some from the Brazilian Olympiad in Informatics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About SPC</title>
      <link>https://spcubco.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spcubco.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>The Sport Programming Club (SPC) is a club dedicated to foster a problem-solving community on the UBC Okanagan Campus.
We participate in many programming competitions such as Google Code Jam, Facebook Hacker Cup and ACM ICPC. If you are interested in competing in those or just want to improve your problem-solving skills, just come by our meetings at Mondays from 19:00 to 21:00, FIP 124. Pizza provided!
Connect with us on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://spcubco.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spcubco.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>https://spcubco.github.io/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spcubco.github.io/training/</guid>
      <description>We meet weekly to discuss problems from past contests and introduce new techniques. We support all our members and will try our best to help you train.
We also encourage members with more available time to follow this training sheet. The more you train, the better problem solver you become.
We also provide 1-on-1 coaching. If you are interested, send us an email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Events</title>
      <link>https://spcubco.github.io/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spcubco.github.io/calendar/</guid>
      <description>This calendar contains the events we encourage our members to participate.
ACM ICPC  November 9th at UBC Vancouver More information TBA  UBC Programming Contest  Practice round at 11:00-12:30pm PDT Contest at 1:00-5:00pm PDT SCI 234  Google Code Jam  Qualification Round - April 5 from 16:00 until April 6 19:00.  Google Kick Start  Round B - April 20 from 16:00 to 19:00 Round A - Mar 23 from 21:00 to 00:00.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>