<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sports Programming Club</title>
    <link>https://spcubco.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sports Programming Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 10:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://spcubco.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetings 2020</title>
      <link>https://spcubco.github.io/posts/2019/09/meetings-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spcubco.github.io/posts/2019/09/meetings-2020/</guid>
      <description>This page will be updated with the content of the meetings.
The password asked to join the contest is &amp;ldquo;okanagan&amp;rdquo;, without quotes.
Meeting 9 (First of 2020)  Brute force to minimize distance Brute force math example Brute force to find the closest sum Find all fraction permutations Arrange seating given restrictions Create the minimum sum code  Meeting 8  Dijkstra&#39;s algorithm Dijkstra&#39;s algorithm for sparse graphs Try your Dijkstra implementation here Maze problem Example of Dijkstra with a twist  Meeting 6  Discussion of Prefix Sum Discussion of Fenwick Tree Try cumulative sums here Try your Fenwick Tree here Inversion Count  Meeting 5  Implementation of Kruskal&#39;s algorithm Discussion of Kruskal&#39;s Test your implementation here  Meeting 4  Contest Geeks for Geeks Implementation Problem 1 Problem 2 Problem 3 Problem 4  Meeting 3  Contest  Meeting 2  Contest  Meeting 1  Contest  Useful Links  uHunt Competitive Programming Book VisuAlgo Training Sheet  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetings 2019</title>
      <link>https://spcubco.github.io/posts/2019/01/meetings-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spcubco.github.io/posts/2019/01/meetings-2019/</guid>
      <description>This page will be updated with the content of the meetings.
The password asked to join the contest is &amp;ldquo;okanagan&amp;rdquo;, without quotes.
Meeting 9 In this meeting, we will not use vjudge. Instead, we will use problems from Univerity of Erechim&#39;s online judge (URI). We opted to do that because after searching on the internet, there were not many problems that were straightforward DFS/BFS problems. Hence, we opted to pick some from the Brazilian Olympiad in Informatics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>